onlineprizedraws.com 2014-07-14

# 

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy notice applies to us the competition organizer OfferService BV, and our website www.onlineprizedraws.com 

**Personal Information**  
I agree that the contest organizer may validate my phone number and email address through an electronic process called 'pinging'. The purpose for this process is to ensure that the phone number that is registered is a real phone number for entry into the prize draw and direct marketing purposes.

We collect and hold your personal information. This includes the information you choose to provide us when you voluntarily register, such as your name, address, date of birth, and telephone number.

This also includes the information you provide when you answer questions on our website to participate in contests, such as information regarding you and your household, your demographic and lifestyle, your buying behaviour, and your preferences and interests in relation to products, communication and media.

We collect information about the pages you view, and the links you click, including advertisements, through common internet technologies such as cookies and web beacons, and your IP-address, which is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet.

**Uses  
**We conduct internal surveys, analyse and compile in reports, in aggregated form, the information that is collected. We use the aggregated information to design the offers of our select partners and competition prize sponsors as effectively as possible.

The information we collect also enables us to optimize our service to you by:

  * Greeting you personally and providing a more personalized experience when you visit our website.
  * Displaying content and advertising customized to your preferences and interests. For example, offers for pet owners are displayed solely to users with pets.
  * From time to time and only with your permission, informing you about the services and products of our selected partners, competition organizers and prize sponsors. When you are registering, you can decide and choose to opt-in if you are interested in receiving this information, or not if you would prefer not to receive such information.

**Sharing**  
Except as described in this privacy notice, we keep your personal information confidential. We do not disclose your personal information for identification purposes or convey it to third parties if you have not opted-in upon registration with us.

The employees of the competition organizer have access to only the information they require for their work.

The case of winning represents an exception. If you win, you give us your explicit permission to publish your first name, place of origin and a photograph of you on one of the competition organizer's internet pages.

Please note that due to legal reasons an obligation to release your information can exist. For events that are completely or partially sponsored by third parties, you also provide the third parties with your information, as far as you choose to do so. We are unable to control these third parties' policies and practices for the protection of your privacy.

Please note that we may transfer, sell or assign the collected information to any entity to which we divest all or a portion of our business, or to such of our clients as we deem appropriate.

**Correction and Deletion of personal information**  
You can request that your personal information be corrected. You can also request that your account be deleted. To do so, please send us an email, at info@onlineprizedraws.com, or write to OfferService BV, 1e van Swindenstraat 381, 1093 GB Amsterdam, The Netherlands.  We reserve the right to store information concerning registered users who have violated user conditions or whose access has been cancelled in order to avoid repeated misuse.

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is our utmost priority. We store and protect all personal information that you submit to us in accordance with high security standards and to the best of our knowledge.

The information is filed in a databank server by storing the user entries. This server meets all current standards corresponding to safety precautions. It is protected not only against digital but also physical attacks.

However, we do not assume responsibility for the publication of the information due to errors during transmission or due to unauthorized access by third parties. You should be aware that information which you voluntarily reveal over the Internet, for example, in discussion forums, via e-mail or in chat rooms can be used by others. We do not monitor the actions of our visitors and registered users. If you reveal personal information, you do so at your own risk and understand that this information can be collected and used by others. Whether you receive unwanted messages or not is up to you because you alone are responsible for the concealment of your e-mail address.

**Other information**  
This complete privacy notice will be available to you at all times. It may be altered from time to time. Should you require further information, or should you have any objections or questions, please e-mail us at info@onlineprizedraws.com, or write to OfferService BV, 1e van Swindenstraat 381, 1093 GB Amsterdam, The Netherlands.
